[Music]
so uh myself so tan I'm vice president
for health agency so we take care of
Health Products so recently we talked
about the Elevate product that we have
launched so there are the four major
features about the product that I will
again R you so in finite
was one where a customer can take an x
amount of n number of amount of claim in
his once once in his lifetime then was a
power booster can where in his policy
actually uh gets doubled every year so
if he buys a 10 lakh policy it becomes
20 lakhs the next year this is again an
add on cover next 10 years the 10 lakh
policy will become a one CR policy and
so on and so forth right third was the
jump start that we talked about where in
a customer if he has a ped so he can get
a cover from 31st day as in the normal
policy if you see PD has different
different uh somebody covers it in two
years and in three years with jump start
it gets covered in 31st day only then
there was an unlimited some insured
add-on feature that we had where a
customer can buy unlimited some insure
policy so these are the major features
that we have in our product apart from
these features we have some 18 add-on
covers that a customer can buy depending
upon his needs so we had got in a
modular CHC product right wherein if a
customer needs some of the other add on
he can pick and choose and he can pay
the premium and get his policy done so
now it's totally dependent on the
customer see again this product is again
based on AI that we talked about so
we'll actually give customer and added
Advantage we'll recommend him a plan
this is the best suited plan for that
particular customer so if depending upon
the demography depending upon his family
size depending upon what age he's into
right depend on his income everything so
we'll curate a plan for him and we will
recommend a plan to that customer so
these are the major features that we
have launched in this product what is
the main reason to launch to launch this
product so main reason is that we want
to see again if you see today India as a
country we are only we have only 5%
penetration in health insurance space so
we want to grow we are already number
one in other SE we want to be number one
in health space as
well what the present market share what
so q1 if I talk about uh is 2.9% market
share in health space and overall health
this is retail health I'm talking about
2.9% and overall health space if we see
uh taking into represent a group
business as well so we are at
11.4% and see we as an organization want
to be at the
top sorry basically see that is called a
jump start feature where in there are
five lifestyle dises so there is aama
there's obesity hypertension hyper
lipidemia so all these diseases are
taken into these are called lifestyle
diseases so if a customer Ops for that
jump start addon cover he starts getting
his ped covered pre-existing disease
covered from the 31st day if he doesn't
take that cover it is a threee waiting
period in the PED if he takes that cover
it comes down to 31 days only this this
this is all including cancer only five
lifestyle diseases obesity hypertension
hyper lipidemia
asema so these are for
lifestyle thank you thank you
[Music]